<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>english on Castálio Podcast</title><link>https://castalio.info/tags/english/</link><description>Recent content in english on Castálio Podcast</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>© 2011-{year} Castálio Podcast</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://castalio.info/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 142: David Kopec - Classic Computer Science Problems in Python</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-142-david-kopec-classic-computer-science-problems-in-python/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-142-david-kopec-classic-computer-science-problems-in-python/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Our guest for today's episode is an assistant professor of Computer Science and Innovation at Champlain College in Burlington, Vermont. He is the author of Dart for Absolute Beginners (Apress, 2014), Classic Computer Science Problems in Swift (Manning, 2018) and, the recently released, Classic Computer Science Problems in Python (Manning, 2019). Also he is active in the open source community as the author of several popular Swift data structure projects.</description></item><item><title>Episode 131: Justin Keyes - Neovim</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-131-justin-keyes-neovi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-131-justin-keyes-neovi/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Our guest for today’s episode is Neovim maintainer, Vim contributor, and a software engineer. It is with a great pleasure that we welcome Justin Keyes to our podcast
Listen while you read the show notes! MP3 OGG We talked about these topics How he started programming carrer What kind of software he is developing What is the programming language he uses at work How did he get started with Vim and its community Did he try Emacs?</description></item><item><title>Episódio 126: John Roa - PyCon Colombia</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-126-john-roa-pycon-colombia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-126-john-roa-pycon-colombia/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Our guest for today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a passionate self taught team lead and software developer. Cyclist that loves speed. Director of Engineering at LendingFront and PyCon Colombia chief organizer. Our guest today is John Roa and we are going to be talking about PyCon Colombia which is going to happen in Medellin, Colombia through February 9, 10 and 11 - 2018.</description></item><item><title>Episode 119: Carol Nichols - Rust Language</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-119-carol-nichols-rust-language/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episode-119-carol-nichols-rust-language/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Today, we are going to be talking about one of the new programming languages that have attracted attention from programmers and companies around the world. Presented by Mozilla Research as a &amp;quot;Safe, Practical and Concurrent&amp;quot; solution and with the promise of solving known systems programming problems, Rust is also a multi-paradigm and multi-purpose language. And we'll learn more about Rust with Carol Nichols one of its core-developers and author of The Rust Programming Language book.</description></item><item><title>Episódio 114: Mariatta Wijaya - CPython</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-114-mariatta-wijaya-cpython/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-114-mariatta-wijaya-cpython/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Nossa convidada de hoje é engenheira de sofware em Vancouver, Canadá, é co-organizadora da PyLadies Vancouver e da conferencia PyCascades. Ela também é Python Core Developer, contribuindo com a documentação oficial do Python, Python Developer's Guide, Python Core Workflow, e o site python.org. Ela é a primeira pessoa que entrevistamos neste podcast que tem créditos em filmes no IMDB.</description></item><item><title>Episódio 106: Dan Bader</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-106-dan-bader/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-106-dan-bader/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Nosso convidado de hoje se intitula &amp;ldquo;a complete python nut&amp;rdquo;, gosta de cozinhar comida vegetariana, é o autor do livro Python Tricks, recentemente se tornou o mantenedor do site http://pep8.org, publicou vários vídeos excelentes no YouTube, e, se não fosse o bastante, ele iniciou um projeto chamado PythonistaCafe! É com grande prazer que nos recebemos nosso convidado, Dan Bader.</description></item><item><title>Episódio 83: Tarek Ziadé - Mozilla</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-83-tarek-ziade-mozilla/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-83-tarek-ziade-mozilla/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Nosso convidado de hoje é um desenvolvedor Python que trabalha na Mozilla no time de Serviços, escreveu vários livros sobre Python em inglês e francês, pai de 3, é um corredor ávido, usuário Vim e trabalha de Dijon, na França. É com grande prazer que trazemos mais uma entrevista em inglês e conversamos com o Tarek Ziadé.
Já vai aquecendo o seu inglês porque de agora em diante o post será escrito nesta lingua.</description></item><item><title>Episódio 80: Kenneth Reitz - Python Requests</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-80-kenneth-reitz-python-requests/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-80-kenneth-reitz-python-requests/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
Nosso convidado de hoje é o criador do Python Requests: HTTP para Humanos, atualmente trabalha no Heroku com um título bem interessante, PythonOverLord, possui uma coleção incrível de fotos no Instagram, e possui seu próprio Import This podcast. Ele também escreveu o &amp;quot;Hitchhiker's Guide to Python&amp;quot;, um livro de boas práticas em Python que foi, coincidentemente publicado pela O'Reilly em Setembro e todo o lucro das vendas está sendo doado para a fundação Django Girls.</description></item><item><title>Episódio 73: Python Brasil 12 - Parte 1</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-73-python-brasil-12-parte-1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/episodio-73-python-brasil-12-parte-1/</guid><description>Olá pessoal e sejam bem-vindos à mais um episódio do Castálio Podcast!
No episódio de hoje trazemos um episódio diferente pois fizemos algumas entrevistas ao vivo durante a Python Brasil 12. Foram um total de 4 entrevistas que você irá conferir neste espisódio e no próximo, duas por episódio.
As entrevistas foram realizadas pelo Elyézer Rezende e Bruno Rocha, isso mesmo, agora o Bruno Rocha está participando conosco no Castálio! O Og infelizmente não estava presente nas entrevistas ao vivo, mas está presente no episódio.</description></item><item><title>Pete Savage: Git In The Trenches (GITT)</title><link>https://castalio.info/episodes/pete-savage-git-in-the-trenches-gitt/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2011 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://castalio.info/episodes/pete-savage-git-in-the-trenches-gitt/</guid><description>First off I'd like to welcome all the new visitors to this podcast's 17th episode and the very first one done in English! This podcast was born out of my curiosity of getting to know a bit more about the people I have met, whether in person or online, and go beyond the superficial information about them. So instead of just talking about what I already knew, I wanted to focus on what I didn't know.</description></item></channel></rss>